<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sports &#8211; News 2pi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.2pi.se/category/sports/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.2pi.se</link>
	<description>Breaking News, Sports &#38; Entertainment</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 11:57:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Mbappe &#8216;threatened&#8217; by PSG diehards</title>
		<link>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/mbappe-threatened-by-psg-diehards/</link>
					<comments>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/mbappe-threatened-by-psg-diehards/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 11:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.2pi.se/?p=22</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It is only a matter of time before Kylian Mbappe leaves PSG for Real Madrid. Even if there is no official announcement, it is certain that Mbappe will be known as a Real player from June 30 onwards. In the meantime, Spanish media Marca has also confirmed the news that Mbappe has signed a contract ... <a title="Mbappe &#8216;threatened&#8217; by PSG diehards" class="read-more" href="https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/mbappe-threatened-by-psg-diehards/" aria-label="Read more about Mbappe &#8216;threatened&#8217; by PSG diehards">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It is only a matter of time before Kylian Mbappe leaves PSG for Real Madrid. Even if there is no official announcement, it is certain that Mbappe will be known as a Real player from June 30 onwards. In the meantime, Spanish media Marca has also confirmed the news that Mbappe has signed a contract with Real. Mbappé&#8217;s decision to leave the club is starting to have an impact in Paris.</p>



<p>Mbappe has not been given the opportunity to play the full 90 minutes in three consecutive matches at PSG. The European media also reported that the French star was angry about this. PSG coach Luis Enrique told Mbappe that he had to get used to playing without him. However, Mbappe believes he is being left out deliberately due to his decision to leave the club.</p>



<p>The next few months are going to be difficult for Mbappe not only on the field but also off the field. A few days ago, French media outlet Lequip reported that Mbappe&#8217;s representatives had asked PSG&#8217;s hard-line supporters&#8217; group, Collective Ultras Paris, not to give two before the official announcement. But now the situation is probably changing.</p>



<p>A banner, which was placed outside the Parc des Princes, PSG&#8217;s ground, went viral on social media yesterday. The banner read, &#8216;KM (Kylian Mbappe): Waiting for June 30.&#8217; It is understood that PSG&#8217;s staunch supporters are waiting to send Mbappe off. They may now want to put the Mbappe-chapter behind them and look ahead.</p>



<p>One can now raise the question whether Mbappe will be easily abandoned by PSG&#8217;s staunch supporters. Earlier they made life miserable for Lionel Messi and Neymar while playing for PSG. The pitch was constantly passed, and even in front of Neymar&#8217;s house, the Collective Ultras Paris protested. It remains to be seen whether Mbappe will have to fall into such a situation in the coming days.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, the French media Lequip reported that Mbappe is now uncomfortable at PSG. At this stage of the season, he cannot accept the fact that the news of his decision to leave the club was leaked. He thinks that in such a situation the team can also suffer. Besides, the World Cup winning footballer also thinks that PSG did not respect his decision by leaking the news of leaving the club.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/mbappe-threatened-by-psg-diehards/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
