<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; News 2pi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.2pi.se/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.2pi.se</link>
	<description>Breaking News, Sports &#38; Entertainment</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:00:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Interest in underground rooms is growing in Sweden</title>
		<link>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/interest-in-underground-rooms-is-growing-in-sweden/</link>
					<comments>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/interest-in-underground-rooms-is-growing-in-sweden/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.2pi.se/?p=25</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From the outside, it looks like ten other ordinary houses in Sweden. Earlier it was a school building. Now in use as a private house. It is surrounded by agricultural land. The house made of red wood is quite big. But below the house there is an underground room like a guest house. The house ... <a title="Interest in underground rooms is growing in Sweden" class="read-more" href="https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/interest-in-underground-rooms-is-growing-in-sweden/" aria-label="Read more about Interest in underground rooms is growing in Sweden">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>From the outside, it looks like ten other ordinary houses in Sweden. Earlier it was a school building. Now in use as a private house. It is surrounded by agricultural land. The house made of red wood is quite big. But below the house there is an underground room like a guest house.</p>



<p>The house is located in the area of Ljungby, Samaland, Königsberg County, Sweden. The underground room of the house has to be entered by stairs. Many people call it the &#8216;hiding cave&#8217;. A 1.25 meter thick concrete structure has been used in its construction. Apart from this, it has orange colored metal doors and special system of light and air entry. It was originally used as a &#8216;bunker&#8217; during the Cold War.</p>



<p>This underground room has an area of 490 square meters. There are two floors with its own kitchen, bar, bedroom, cleaning area, power generation system, carbon filter ventilation facility. This room can also withstand a 500 kg bomb attack.</p>



<p>Fear among Swedes has grown over the past two years after Russian forces began attacking Ukraine. The country is on the way to join the military alliance NATO. Now, fearing Russian attacks, they are turning to such shelters again.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/interest-in-underground-rooms-is-growing-in-sweden/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Harris spoke harshly to Israel</title>
		<link>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/harris-spoke-harshly-to-israel/</link>
					<comments>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/harris-spoke-harshly-to-israel/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 11:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.2pi.se/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[US Vice President Kamala Harris has called for the acceptance of a proposed six-week ceasefire agreement in the Gaza Strip. At the same time, Harris criticized Israel for insufficient aid to Gaza. In a speech given in the US state of Alabama on Sunday, Harris said that in view of the extreme suffering in Gaza, ... <a title="Harris spoke harshly to Israel" class="read-more" href="https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/harris-spoke-harshly-to-israel/" aria-label="Read more about Harris spoke harshly to Israel">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>US Vice President Kamala Harris has called for the acceptance of a proposed six-week ceasefire agreement in the Gaza Strip.</p>



<p>At the same time, Harris criticized Israel for insufficient aid to Gaza.</p>



<p>In a speech given in the US state of Alabama on Sunday, Harris said that in view of the extreme suffering in Gaza, there is an immediate need for a ceasefire of at least six weeks in the Valley, which is now on the negotiation table.</p>



<p>Harris has strongly urged the government of Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to increase aid supplies to Gaza. &#8220;The Israeli government must do more to significantly increase the flow of aid,&#8221; he said. No excuses will work in this case.</p>



<p>This is the strongest comment ever made by a US official on Israel. When US President Joe Biden was under heavy pressure for his support for Israel, his vice president made such comments.</p>



<p>A senior US official said last Saturday that Israel has largely accepted the proposed agreement.</p>



<p>If Hamas agrees to release the most vulnerable hostages, a six-week cease-fire would follow, the proposal said.</p>



<p>Harris urged Hamas to accept the proposed deal. He believes that, under the terms of the agreement, hostages will be released, and a significant amount of relief will be able to reach Gaza.</p>



<p>The US Vice President said that Hamas is claiming that they want a ceasefire. good talk A contract proposal is on the negotiating table. Hamas should agree to this deal.</p>



<p>On October 7 last year, the Palestinian independence armed organization Hamas attacked Israel. Based on information from Israeli officials, AFP says that about 1,160 people were killed in this attack. Most of them are civilians. That day, Hamas took about 250 hostages to Gaza. The Israeli army says the number of hostages now stands at 130. Of these, 31 are believed to have died.</p>



<p>Israel started attacking Gaza from October 7. According to the Hamas government&#8217;s Ministry of Health, more than 30,400 people have been killed in Israeli strikes in Gaza.</p>



<p>Harris is scheduled to meet with Israeli War Cabinet member Benny Gantz in Washington on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/harris-spoke-harshly-to-israel/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
