<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin &#8211; News 2pi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://news.2pi.se/author/admin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://news.2pi.se</link>
	<description>Breaking News, Sports &#38; Entertainment</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:00:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Interest in underground rooms is growing in Sweden</title>
		<link>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/interest-in-underground-rooms-is-growing-in-sweden/</link>
					<comments>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/interest-in-underground-rooms-is-growing-in-sweden/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.2pi.se/?p=25</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From the outside, it looks like ten other ordinary houses in Sweden. Earlier it was a school building. Now in use as a private house. It is surrounded by agricultural land. The house made of red wood is quite big. But below the house there is an underground room like a guest house. The house ... <a title="Interest in underground rooms is growing in Sweden" class="read-more" href="https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/interest-in-underground-rooms-is-growing-in-sweden/" aria-label="Read more about Interest in underground rooms is growing in Sweden">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>From the outside, it looks like ten other ordinary houses in Sweden. Earlier it was a school building. Now in use as a private house. It is surrounded by agricultural land. The house made of red wood is quite big. But below the house there is an underground room like a guest house.</p>



<p>The house is located in the area of Ljungby, Samaland, Königsberg County, Sweden. The underground room of the house has to be entered by stairs. Many people call it the &#8216;hiding cave&#8217;. A 1.25 meter thick concrete structure has been used in its construction. Apart from this, it has orange colored metal doors and special system of light and air entry. It was originally used as a &#8216;bunker&#8217; during the Cold War.</p>



<p>This underground room has an area of 490 square meters. There are two floors with its own kitchen, bar, bedroom, cleaning area, power generation system, carbon filter ventilation facility. This room can also withstand a 500 kg bomb attack.</p>



<p>Fear among Swedes has grown over the past two years after Russian forces began attacking Ukraine. The country is on the way to join the military alliance NATO. Now, fearing Russian attacks, they are turning to such shelters again.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/interest-in-underground-rooms-is-growing-in-sweden/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mbappe &#8216;threatened&#8217; by PSG diehards</title>
		<link>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/mbappe-threatened-by-psg-diehards/</link>
					<comments>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/mbappe-threatened-by-psg-diehards/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 11:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.2pi.se/?p=22</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It is only a matter of time before Kylian Mbappe leaves PSG for Real Madrid. Even if there is no official announcement, it is certain that Mbappe will be known as a Real player from June 30 onwards. In the meantime, Spanish media Marca has also confirmed the news that Mbappe has signed a contract ... <a title="Mbappe &#8216;threatened&#8217; by PSG diehards" class="read-more" href="https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/mbappe-threatened-by-psg-diehards/" aria-label="Read more about Mbappe &#8216;threatened&#8217; by PSG diehards">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It is only a matter of time before Kylian Mbappe leaves PSG for Real Madrid. Even if there is no official announcement, it is certain that Mbappe will be known as a Real player from June 30 onwards. In the meantime, Spanish media Marca has also confirmed the news that Mbappe has signed a contract with Real. Mbappé&#8217;s decision to leave the club is starting to have an impact in Paris.</p>



<p>Mbappe has not been given the opportunity to play the full 90 minutes in three consecutive matches at PSG. The European media also reported that the French star was angry about this. PSG coach Luis Enrique told Mbappe that he had to get used to playing without him. However, Mbappe believes he is being left out deliberately due to his decision to leave the club.</p>



<p>The next few months are going to be difficult for Mbappe not only on the field but also off the field. A few days ago, French media outlet Lequip reported that Mbappe&#8217;s representatives had asked PSG&#8217;s hard-line supporters&#8217; group, Collective Ultras Paris, not to give two before the official announcement. But now the situation is probably changing.</p>



<p>A banner, which was placed outside the Parc des Princes, PSG&#8217;s ground, went viral on social media yesterday. The banner read, &#8216;KM (Kylian Mbappe): Waiting for June 30.&#8217; It is understood that PSG&#8217;s staunch supporters are waiting to send Mbappe off. They may now want to put the Mbappe-chapter behind them and look ahead.</p>



<p>One can now raise the question whether Mbappe will be easily abandoned by PSG&#8217;s staunch supporters. Earlier they made life miserable for Lionel Messi and Neymar while playing for PSG. The pitch was constantly passed, and even in front of Neymar&#8217;s house, the Collective Ultras Paris protested. It remains to be seen whether Mbappe will have to fall into such a situation in the coming days.</p>



<p>Meanwhile, the French media Lequip reported that Mbappe is now uncomfortable at PSG. At this stage of the season, he cannot accept the fact that the news of his decision to leave the club was leaked. He thinks that in such a situation the team can also suffer. Besides, the World Cup winning footballer also thinks that PSG did not respect his decision by leaking the news of leaving the club.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/mbappe-threatened-by-psg-diehards/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kate is excited about the youngsters</title>
		<link>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/kate-is-excited-about-the-youngsters/</link>
					<comments>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/kate-is-excited-about-the-youngsters/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 11:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.2pi.se/?p=19</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[May his age never increase. When he was in his twenties, he became a star. Many stars have come since then, but Kate Winslet&#8217;s appeal has decreased so much? After Covid, when there was a lot of discussion about the series than the movie, Kate surprised everyone by appearing in the HBO series &#8216;Mayor of ... <a title="Kate is excited about the youngsters" class="read-more" href="https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/kate-is-excited-about-the-youngsters/" aria-label="Read more about Kate is excited about the youngsters">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>May his age never increase. When he was in his twenties, he became a star. Many stars have come since then, but Kate Winslet&#8217;s appeal has decreased so much? After Covid, when there was a lot of discussion about the series than the movie, Kate surprised everyone by appearing in the HBO series &#8216;Mayor of Easttown&#8217;.</p>



<p>The 48-year-old British actress is back with the new series &#8216;The Regime&#8217;. He came to &#8216;The Today Show&#8217; to promote the series and talked about various topics.</p>



<p>Kate rose to stardom with James Cameron&#8217;s Titanic, which was released in 1997. However, the actress feels that the world of entertainment has changed a lot since then.</p>



<p>&#8220;Everything has changed a lot,&#8221; Kate said. This has been the case for today&#8217;s young female artists. They have created a position for themselves since the beginning. They have something unique. They know how to hold their own. All these young actresses know their importance, stand by each other.</p>



<p>Kate finds it amazing how the landscape of the entertainment world has changed with the arrival of young actresses on the scene. According to Kate, it is very exciting to see young people making such an impact. Young people should be by their side, they should be cared for.</p>



<p>Kate Winslet was seen in the new series &#8216;The Regime&#8217;. The first episode of the series aired yesterday. Each episode of the six-part series will be released consecutively till April 7. The HBO political satire series was created by Steven Fierce and Jessica Hobbs. The series stars Kate Winslet as the chancellor of a fictional European country. Apart from Kate, the series also stars Martha Plimpton, Andrea Risebrough, Hugh Grant.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/kate-is-excited-about-the-youngsters/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Harris spoke harshly to Israel</title>
		<link>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/harris-spoke-harshly-to-israel/</link>
					<comments>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/harris-spoke-harshly-to-israel/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 11:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://news.2pi.se/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[US Vice President Kamala Harris has called for the acceptance of a proposed six-week ceasefire agreement in the Gaza Strip. At the same time, Harris criticized Israel for insufficient aid to Gaza. In a speech given in the US state of Alabama on Sunday, Harris said that in view of the extreme suffering in Gaza, ... <a title="Harris spoke harshly to Israel" class="read-more" href="https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/harris-spoke-harshly-to-israel/" aria-label="Read more about Harris spoke harshly to Israel">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>US Vice President Kamala Harris has called for the acceptance of a proposed six-week ceasefire agreement in the Gaza Strip.</p>



<p>At the same time, Harris criticized Israel for insufficient aid to Gaza.</p>



<p>In a speech given in the US state of Alabama on Sunday, Harris said that in view of the extreme suffering in Gaza, there is an immediate need for a ceasefire of at least six weeks in the Valley, which is now on the negotiation table.</p>



<p>Harris has strongly urged the government of Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to increase aid supplies to Gaza. &#8220;The Israeli government must do more to significantly increase the flow of aid,&#8221; he said. No excuses will work in this case.</p>



<p>This is the strongest comment ever made by a US official on Israel. When US President Joe Biden was under heavy pressure for his support for Israel, his vice president made such comments.</p>



<p>A senior US official said last Saturday that Israel has largely accepted the proposed agreement.</p>



<p>If Hamas agrees to release the most vulnerable hostages, a six-week cease-fire would follow, the proposal said.</p>



<p>Harris urged Hamas to accept the proposed deal. He believes that, under the terms of the agreement, hostages will be released, and a significant amount of relief will be able to reach Gaza.</p>



<p>The US Vice President said that Hamas is claiming that they want a ceasefire. good talk A contract proposal is on the negotiating table. Hamas should agree to this deal.</p>



<p>On October 7 last year, the Palestinian independence armed organization Hamas attacked Israel. Based on information from Israeli officials, AFP says that about 1,160 people were killed in this attack. Most of them are civilians. That day, Hamas took about 250 hostages to Gaza. The Israeli army says the number of hostages now stands at 130. Of these, 31 are believed to have died.</p>



<p>Israel started attacking Gaza from October 7. According to the Hamas government&#8217;s Ministry of Health, more than 30,400 people have been killed in Israeli strikes in Gaza.</p>



<p>Harris is scheduled to meet with Israeli War Cabinet member Benny Gantz in Washington on Monday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://news.2pi.se/2024/03/04/harris-spoke-harshly-to-israel/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
